### Search

 Everywhere Threads This forum This thread

Search titles only

By: 

Search [Advanced search…](https://www.car-seat.org/search/)

Menu

* * *

* * *

Install the app

Install

* Welcome! [CLICK HERE to ask a question](https://www.car-seat.org/index.php?forums/car-seats-child-safety-seat-questions-and-advice.4/post-thread) about the best carseat or safest choice for your family. Visitor posts subject to approval. _Please note that some threads are old and may contain obsolete or outdated information. Please verify all advice with your owner's manuals and state law._

JavaScript is disabled. For a better experience, please enable JavaScript in your browser before proceeding.

You are using an out of date browser. It may not display this or other websites correctly.  
You should upgrade or use an [alternative browser](https://www.google.com/chrome/).

Privacy Policy
==============

* Thread starter [Admin](https://www.car-seat.org/members/admin.2/)
* Start date [May 10, 2011](https://www.car-seat.org/threads/privacy-policy.131533/)

Status

Not open for further replies.

#### [Admin](https://www.car-seat.org/members/admin.2/)

##### Admin - Webmaster

**Car-Seat.org Privacy Policy  
  
Last Updated May 1, 2018**​

Carseat Media LLC (dba Car-Seat.Org) understands and respects your concerns about privacy. This notice describes Car-Seat.Org’s privacy policy as it pertains to its websites at [www.Car-Safety.org](http://www.car-safety.org/), [www.car-seat.org](http://www.car-seat.org/), and [www.carseatblog.com](http://www.carseatblog.com/) (the "Websites"). We may from time-to-time revise this privacy policy, and the date of last revision will be available at the top of this page, so please be sure to check back periodically. **By visiting the Websites, you are acknowledging and accepting this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Websites after changes have been posted to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.  
  
What information we collect:** Car-Seat.Org may ask for and collect from you personally identifiable information at certain points throughout the Websites. Depending on the information and/or services you request, you may be asked to provide your name, email address and other information. Once you provide your personal information, you are not anonymous to Car-Seat.Org.  
  
In addition to the information you knowingly provide, Car-Seat.Org may collect the domain names and IP addresses of its visitors, along with usage statistics (e.g., types of web browsers and operating systems used) and browsing history. This data is used to more efficiently operate Car-Seat.Org’s business, promote our products and services and administer the Websites. Car-Seat.Org may combine this information with the personally identifiable information it collects.  
  
How Car-Seat.Org uses your information: Car-Seat.Org may use your information:  
  
• To provide you with personalized content.  
• To process and respond to inquiries.  
• For the purposes for which you provided the information.  
• To improve the content and navigability of the Websites.  
• To alert you to new Website features, special events, products and services, and to deliver newsletters from which you may opt out.  
• To enforce the Terms of Use.  
  
In the future, we may sell some or all or our assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the event of a sale of our assets including our database, customer information will be transferred. We will require buyers to honor our privacy policy.  
  
**Information Sharing with Unaffiliated Third Parties:** Car-Seat.Org may disclose your personally identifiable information to another entity (i) for purposes of outsourcing one or more of the functions described in the previous section; (ii) to confirm or update information provided by you; (iii) to inform you of important information; and/or (iv) as a part of a sale of assets as described in the previous section. We may also share your information in response to a subpoena, legal order or official request, when we believe you have acted in violation of the [Terms of Use](http://www.car-seat.org/showthread.php?t=170684) or the Code of Conduct (including [User Guidelines](http://www.car-seat.org/announcement.php?f=6)), or when we believe that doing so may protect your safety or the safety of others.  
  
Information Sharing with Affiliated Companies: We may share your personally identifiable information with other companies in the Car-Seat.Org family, co-branding partners and network partners, and will require the recipient to comply with the provisions of this privacy policy.  
  
**Non-personally identifiable information:** We may aggregate and/or anonymize information we collect so that the information does not identify you. Our use and disclosure of aggregated, anonymized, and other non-personally identifiable information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy, and we may disclose it to third parties without limitation.  
How we collect information: In addition to the methods described above, we may also collect information using cookies, web beacons or similar technologies. These methods permit us to collect various types of information, including which pages you visit, which of our email messages you read, and other information.  
  
**How we protect information:** Car-Seat.Org attempts to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information. Our servers are protected by reasonable physical and electronic security measures.  
  
**How you can view or update your personal information:** To ensure that you have as much control over your personally identifiable information as possible, you may update your information by contacting us at [webmaster@car-seat.org](mailto:webmaster@car-seat.org) or utilizing the Account Access (User CP) section of the Website. We will use reasonable efforts to process any change you make; provided, however, that requests to delete information are subject to Car-Seat.Org’s internal reporting and retention policies and all applicable legal obligations.  
  
**Targeted Advertising:** We may use [third-party advertising companies](http://www.car-seat.org/showpost.php?p=1777308&postcount=2) to serve ads when you visit our Websites. Some of these companies may place cookies on your browser to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to Car-Seat.Org and other websites and use that information in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. To learn more about this practice, its benefits, or about your choice to opt-out of this practice, see [http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout\_nonppii.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). These advertisements, insertions, and automatically generated links include, but are not limited to, affiliate and advertising relationships with [Google](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites), [sovrn / commerce](http://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/), [Conversant](http://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy), [Skimlinks](http://skimlinks.com/privacy-policy) and/or other networks. Car-Seat.Org (and its websites including [CarseatBlog.com](http://carseatblog.com/)) is a participant in the [Amazon Services LLC Associates Program](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/help/operating/agreement), an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to [Amazon.com](http://amazon.com/) and affiliated sites.  
  
**Children:** These Websites are not directed toward children under 13 years of age nor does Car-Seat.Org knowingly collect information from children under 13. If you are under 13, please do not submit any personally identifiable information to Car-Seat.Org.  
  
**Visitors from outside the USA and Canada:** Due to country-specific regulations and standards involving child safety seat certification and sale, Car-Seat.Org is targeted to and intended only for viewers in the USA and Canada. Car-Seat.Org and its websites (including CarseatBlog) do not target information to viewers in the European Union and do not knowingly collect information from anyone located in the EU. _Registrations and posts from visitors in European Union countries cannot be accepted at this time._ If you are a citizen, resident or located in the EU, you must not register, submit a comment or any personally identifiable information to Car-Seat.Org. Existing members now located in the EU may request permanent account deletion and/or purge of member information by [contacting Admin](https://www.car-seat.org/conversations/add?to=Admin). Email addresses submitted for comments at CarseatBlog are for verification and spam prevention only, Carseat Media LLC does not otherwise process any personal information for any purpose. Carseat Media LLC does not directly sell any products and does not provide any information or service for outside of the USA and Canada.  
  
**Links:** The Websites may contain links to third-party websites. Car-Seat.Org is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.  
  
**Contacts:** If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at [webmaster@car-seat.org](mailto:webmaster@car-seat.org) or by [Private Message to Admin](http://www.car-seat.org/private.php?do=newpm&u=1).  
  
Copyright © 2011-2020 Car-Seat.Org. All rights reserved.

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|     | ADS |     |

#### [Admin](https://www.car-seat.org/members/admin.2/)

##### Admin - Webmaster

We respect your privacy. Really. Car-Seat.Org has never sold or processed user data in almost 20 years since our site began. We do not collect data on unregistered visitors and have never shared any personal information without explicit written consent from a member. Visitors may even post anonymously as an unregistered guest, subject to moderator approval delays. Members are welcome to use anonymous usernames and email addresses, but must confirm an email address to be approved as a registered member. IP addresses are only scanned against malicious activity databases upon registration and posting to prevent spammer, hacker and other nuisance posts. IP addresses may be stored for a limited time but only if a user submits a post or message. Unlike facebook and other services, we do not require any other personal information unless voluntarily submitted by the member, such as in the case of a prize or contest award shared with the sponsor/shipper after obtaining written permission from the winner.

Last edited: Apr 25, 2020

Status

Not open for further replies.

Share:

Facebook Twitter Reddit Pinterest Tumblr WhatsApp Email Share Link

### Car-Seat.Org Facebook Group

### Sponsors

### Forum statistics

Threads

219,694

Messages

2,197,016

Members

13,552

Latest member

You must read your carseat and vehicle owner’s manual and understand any relevant state laws. These are the rules you must follow to restrain your children safely. All opinions at Car-Seat.Org are those of the individual author for informational purposes only, and do not necessarily reflect any policy or position of Carseat Media LLC. Car-Seat.Org makes no representations as to accuracy, completeness, currentness, suitability, or validity of any information on this site and will not be liable for any errors, omissions, or delays in this information or any losses, injuries, or damages arising from its display or use. All information is provided on an as-is basis. If you are unsure about information provided to you, please visit a local certified technician. Before posting or using our website you must read and agree to our [TERMS](https://www.car-seat.org/showthread.php?170684-Terms-of-Service).

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |

Please  [Support Car-Seat.Org](https://www.car-seat.org/index.php?threads/please-support-car-seat-org-advertising-sponsorships-and-subscriptions.19160/)  with your purchases of infant, convertible, combination and boosters seats from our premier sponsors above.  
Shop travel systems, strollers and baby gear from Britax, Chicco, Clek, Combi, Evenflo, First Years, Graco, Maxi-Cosi, Nuna, Safety 1st, Diono & more! ©2001-2022 Carseat Media LLC

* This site uses cookies to help personalise content, tailor your experience and to keep you logged in if you register.  
    By continuing to use this site, you are consenting to our use of cookies.
